http://janweb.icdi.wvu.edu/privacy-statement.cfm

Close Menu
Close
For EmployersFor IndividualsFor OthersADA LibraryA to Z ListsAccommodation SearchPublications & ArticlesWhat's NewHot TopicsTrainingEventsNewsletterConsultants’ CornerBlogAbout UsContact Us
A
A
A
Text Size
Print This Page
Privacy Statement
home
JAN's privacy statement
Listen
Thank you for visiting the JAN Website and reviewing JAN's privacy policy. Our privacy policy is clear: JAN collects no personal information about you when you visit our Website unless you choose to provide that information to us. If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the Website, read pages, or download information, JAN gathers and stores certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. JAN automatically collects and stores only the following information about your visit:
1. The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our Web site;
2. The date and time you access our site; and
3. The pages you visit.
JAN uses this information to help make the site more useful to visitors and to learn about the number of visitors to our site. JAN does not track or record information about individuals and their visits. If you choose to provide JAN with personal information by providing an e-mail with your personal information and submitting it through our Website, JAN uses that information to respond to your message and to help provide you the information requested. All correspondence is confidential. We do not give information to any other organization or company. Please note that our Website has links to a variety of Websites, which may have other privacy policies.
JAN hopes you enjoy your visit.
Live Chat
Social
Show Reader
Hide Reader
